cintas.com 2019-12-02

# Commitment to Your Privacy | Cintas

Last Updated: 6/24/2019

This site (www.cintas.com, the “Site”) is owned and operated by Cintas Corporation. We have adopted this Privacy Policy to explain the types of information we collect when you use this Site, or any of our mobile or other applications (“Applications” and together with the Site, our “Services”), and how we use and share that information. For clarity, our Services include any promotion which refers to this Privacy Policy for terms regarding the collection and use of your information. While this Privacy Policy applies to information we collect through our Services, it does not apply to our collection of information from other sources (e.g., in person, over the telephone, etc.).

**If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page.** Cintas may change this Privacy Policy at any time to reflect changes in our personal information practices. Thus, it is recommended that you check this Privacy Policy periodically to see if any such changes have been made. Please see the Section titled “Changes to Our Privacy Policy” for information regarding such changes.

##### Information Cintas Collects

We typically collect two kinds of information about you when you use our Services: (a) information that you provide that personally identifies you; and (b) information that does not personally identify you, but that we automatically collect or that you provide us.

Our definition of Personally Identifiable Information includes any information that may be used to specifically identify or contact you. The types of Personally Identifiable Information we may obtain include:

  * Your name, address, telephone number, email or other electronic address and/or company name.
  * Username and password for the account you may establish through our Services.
  * Information you provide in a resume, cover letter or other employment-related materials.
  * In the event that our provision of products and services to you requires it, certain information relating to your desired size and fit.

You generally do not have to give us any Personally Identifiable Information in order to read the content portions of the Services. Whether or not you provide us Personally Identifiable Information is your choice; however, in many instances this type of information is required to participate in the particular activity, realize a benefit we may offer, or gain access to certain content or features available through our Services.

When you visit our Site, we may also collect certain Non-Personally Identifiable Information by automated means, such as cookies (as described in more detail below) or you may provide Non-Personally Identifiable Information to us. Our definition of non-personal information is any information that does not personally identify you. Please note that Non-Personally Identifiable Information can include certain Personally Identifiable Information that has been de-identified; that is, information that has been rendered anonymous. The Non-Personally Identifiable Information we may collect includes:

  * Information about the devices our visitors use to access the Internet (such as the IP address and the device, browser and operating system type).
  * Pages and URLs that refer visitors to our Services, also pages and URLs that visitors exit to once they leave our Site.
  * Dates and times of visits to or use of our Services.
  * Information on actions taken through our Services (such as page views and site navigation patterns).
  * A general geographic location (such as country and city) from which a visitor accesses our Services.
  * Search terms that visitors use to reach our Services. 

Please note, however, that in some jurisdictions, like those in the European Union, things like IP addresses or cookie and mobile device identifiers may also be considered personal information. As a result, to the extent that you are a resident of one of these jurisdictions, such as a resident of the European Economic Area (“EEA”), we may treat some of your information that would otherwise be considered Non-Personally Identifiable Information as Personally Identifiable Information under this Privacy Policy. 

##### Children's Privacy

The features, programs, promotions and other aspects of the Services are not intended for children. If you are less than 18 years old, please do not send any user information to us--including information such as your name, address, or e-mail address. We do not knowingly collect (nor do we wish to collect) any Personally Identifiable Information or other user information from children under the age of 18. In the event that we learn we have collected any personal information from a child under the age of 18, we will delete that information from our database and terminate the corresponding account, if any.

##### Use of Information

Cintas' primary goal in collecting Personally Identifiable Information is to provide the products and services you request, to give you an enjoyable and customized experience while using our Services and interactive features, and to allow us to develop new services to better meet the needs of our users and customers.

We may use the Personally Identifiable Information we obtain about you to:

  * Provide products and services requested by users, communicate with users regarding usage of our products and services, and enhance the operation and experience of our Services.
  * Place, bill, and ship orders, send requested electronic communications to subscribers, send print catalogs, and manage online accounts.
  * Provide administrative notices or communications applicable to your use of our Services.
  * Respond to your enquiries, questions and comments and provide customer support.
  * Process and respond to your application for current and future job opportunities.
  * Should you opt in to receiving such communications, send you promotional information to you that, in some cases, is targeted to your interests and solicit your feedback and input. These communications will contain links for preference management and, where appropriate, unsubscribe links should you decide you do not want to receive further marketing and promotional communications. Please note that if you unsubscribe from receiving marketing and promotional communications from us, you may continue to receive certain transactional messages, such as order confirmations and factual information about your account.
  * Protect against and prevent fraud, unauthorized transactions, claims and other liabilities, and manage risk exposure, including by identifying potential hackers and other unauthorized users.

We use Non-Personally Identifiable Information in order to operate, maintain and manage our Services, to analyze trends and statistics regarding the use of our Services in order to help us understand activity and to monitor and improve our Services. We may use your Non-Personally Identifiable Information by itself or aggregate it with information we have obtained from other customers or other sources. We may, among other things, share your Non-Personally Identifiable Information with our affiliated companies, allow third parties to collect such information directly from you, and/or sell the information to third parties to achieve these and any other business objectives (e.g., generate revenue, form alliances, etc.). However, it is important to remember that your Non-Personally Identifiable Information (whether standing alone or combined with other Non-Personally Identifiable Information) is anonymous information that does not personally identify you.

##### Cookies and analytics

Our Site use a technology called “cookies”. A cookie is a tiny element of data that our Site can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your hard drive so we can recognize you when you return. In particular, we use Google Analytics (“Google Analytics”), a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA as our processor. We use cookies on the pages on our Sites where you are prompted to log in or that are customizable. If you have registered with our Site, these cookies (1) may let us know who you are, (2) may be necessary to access your account information (stored on our computers) in order to deliver products and personalized services, and (3) will provide us and our service providers with information that we will use to personalize our Site in accordance with your preferences.

The cookies may be used to collect and process aggregate tracking information to determine which areas of our Site users like and do not like based on traffic to those areas. This helps us continue to build a better service for you and other Site users. The cookie will not be used to retrieve information from your computer that is unrelated to this Site or your interaction with it. A cookie cannot read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other websites. If you wish, you may instruct your internet browser to prevent cookies from being used or to notify you before a cookie is placed. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use this Site. However, if you have cookies turned on, it enables us to more accurately customize your shopping on this Site. If you decide not to accept cookies from our Site, you may not be able to take advantage of all of the features of our Site.

Preference Based Advertising: We may work with third parties, including advertising companies and website analysis firms, who use cookies and web beacons to collect Non-Personally Identifiable Information when you visit our Site and third party sites. This information, collected through cookies or similar technology, is typically used by these third party advertising companies (i.e., advertising networks) to serve you with advertisements while on third party sites tailored to meet your preferences and needs. If you do not wish to participate in this activity, go to [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/) and follow the simple opt-out process. A couple of important notes about this opt-out tool: (1) it includes all the advertising networks that we may work with, but also many that we do not work with; and (2) it may rely on cookies to ensure that a given advertising network does not collect information about you (“Opt-out Cookies”) – an explanation of how Opt-out Cookies work can be found on [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/). Therefore, if you use different equipment, change web browsers or delete these Opt-out Cookies from your computer, you will need to perform the opt-out task again.

Do Not Track Features:Certain browsers may offer you the option of providing notice to websites that you do not wish for your online activities to be tracked for preference based advertising purposes (“DNT Notice”). Some browsers are, by default, set to provide a DNT Notice, whether or not that reflects your preference. Providing DNT Notice is often touted as a means to ensure that cookies, Web beacons and similar technology are not used for preference based advertising purposes – that is, to restrict the collection of non-personally identifiable information about your online activities for advertising purposes. Unfortunately, given how preference based advertising works, DNT Notices may not effectively accomplish this goal. For this and a variety of other reasons, with respect to our Website, we do not take any action based on browser based DNT Notices. Rather, if you do not wish to participate in preference based advertising activities, you should follow the simple opt-out process identified above.

##### Sharing of Information

Cintas does not sell or share our email lists or Personally Identifiable Information to third parties so that they can independently market to you unless we obtain your consent to do so.

Service Providers: Cintas may transfer (or otherwise make available) your Personal Information to our affiliates, subsidiaries and other third parties who provide services on our behalf. For example, we may use service providers to authorize and process payments, deliver products, send email or other communications, conduct surveys, distribute our products, provide billing and collection services, or host our Site and operate certain of its features. Your personal information may be maintained and processed by our affiliates, subsidiaries and other third party service providers in the US or other jurisdictions. Our service providers, who are bound by written obligations of confidentiality with respect to any information given to them, are given the information they need to perform their designated functions, and we do not authorize them to use or disclose personal information for their own marketing or other purposes. For additional information about the way in which our third-party service providers treat your personal information, contact us as set out below.

Legal/Compliance: Cintas may disclose your Personal Information or other information if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary: (a) to comply with applicable laws or in response to a subpoena, court order, government, or law enforcement request, or other valid legal process; (b) to produce relevant documents or information in connection with litigation, arbitration, mediation, adjudication, government or internal investigations, or other legal or administrative proceedings; (c) to protect the interests, rights, safety, or property of Cintas or others; (d) to enforce the terms of any agreement with Cintas; (e) to operate Cintas' systems properly; (f) or as otherwise required or permitted by applicable law. Further use and/or disclosure of your Personally Identifiable Information by third parties once it has been disclosed by Cintas is not the responsibility of Cintas. Rather, such use and/or disclosure is governed by such parties’ privacy policies.

Sale of Business: We may transfer any Personal Information or other information we have about you as an asset in connection with a merger or sale (including transfers made as part of insolvency or bankruptcy proceedings) involving all or part of Cintas or as part of a corporate reorganization or stock sale or other change in corporate control.

Your California Privacy Rights: Residents of the State of California, under certain provisions of the California Civil Code, have the right to request from companies conducting business in California a list of all third parties to which the company has disclosed certain personally identifiable information as defined under California law during the preceding year for third party direct marketing purposes. In your request, please attest to the fact that you are a California resident and provide a current California address for our response. You may request the information in writing as provided below.

##### Accuracy and Security of Personal Information

To protect your Personal Information in our custody or control from theft, unauthorized access, use, modification and disclosure, and to maintain its accuracy and integrity, we have implemented reasonable technical, physical and administrative security measures. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.

Although we have implemented reasonable safeguards, please note that no electronic transmission of information can be guaranteed to be entirely secure. You acknowledge and agree that we are not responsible for the theft, destruction, or inadvertent disclosure of your Personally Identifiable Information. In the unfortunate event that your “personally identifiable information” (as the term or similar terms are defined by any applicable law requiring notice upon a security breach) is compromised, we may notify you by e-mail (at our sole and absolute discretion) to the last e-mail address you have provided us in the most expedient time reasonable under the circumstances; provided, however, delays in notification may occur while we take necessary measures to determine the scope of the breach and restore reasonable integrity to the system as well as for the legitimate needs of law enforcement if notification would impede a criminal investigation.

##### Accessing Your Personal Information

You may ask for access to your Personally Identifiable Information in our custody and control, ask for your Personally Identifiable Information to be updated or corrected, or ask us to remove your Personally Identifiable Information from our records (subject to our legal obligations to retain such information) by contacting us at [catalogcustomerservice@cintas.com](mailto:catalogcustomerservice@cintas.com) or at the contact information set out below. All requests must include the following information first name, last name, and email address. Cintas will make reasonable efforts to accommodate your request, but reserves the right to impose restrictions and requirements on such access requests, if allowed or required by applicable law.

##### Email Privacy

We ask for your email address for online purchases in order to communicate with you about your orders. If you opt to receive such communications, we also may notify you via email of any specials, promotions, or discounts at Cintas, as well as information on the latest trends in uniforms. If you do not want to receive any marketing or promotional emails, please contact us at [catalogcustomerservice@cintas.com](mailto:catalogcustomerservice@cintas.com). You can also always remove yourself from any Cintas marketing or promotional email list by clicking the unsubscribe link provided in each message. Please note that if you unsubscribe from receiving marketing and promotional communications from us, you may continue to receive certain transactional messages, such as order confirmations and factual information about your account.

##### Secure Shopping

We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) to encrypt your credit card number and payment information. To check if your connection is secure, look at the lower left-hand corner of your browser window. If you see an unbroken key or closed lock (depending on your browser), the SSL is active.

##### Links to other websites

Our Services may contain links to other sites for your convenience and information. These sites may be operated by companies not owned by Cintas and may have their own privacy notices, which you should review if you visit those sites. We are not responsible for the content of any sites not owned by Cintas, any use of those sites, or those sites’ privacy practices.

##### Residents of the European Economic Area

If you are a resident of the EEA, you have certain rights and protections under applicable law regarding the processing of your personal data. The term “personal data” has the meaning given to it by the EU General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”). When we process your personal data, which may include both Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information, as described in this Privacy Policy, we will only do so when we have a legitimate interest in processing your personal data (for example, our legitimate interest in providing requested goods or services to you, responding to your inquiries and sending you marketing communications), when the processing is necessary for the performance of a contract between you and us, when the processing is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which we are subject, or when we have your consent to process your personal data. When processing is based on consent, you have the right to revoke such consent at any time. You also have the right to access personal data we hold about you and to ask that your personal data be corrected, erased, or transferred. You may also have the right to object to, or request that we restrict, certain processing. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, you may contact us as indicated below. If you have a concern about our processing of personal data that we are not able to resolve, you have the right to lodge a complaint with the data privacy authority where you reside. For contact details of your local Data Protection Authority, please see: <https://ec.europa.eu/justice/article-29/structure/data-protection-authorities/index_en.htm>.

##### Changes to our privacy policy

If we make any material changes to our Privacy Policy we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. The date this Privacy Policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You are responsible for ensuring that we have an up-to-date active and deliverable email address for you, and for periodically visiting our website and this Privacy Policy to check for any changes. 

##### Contact Cintas

Cintas welcomes your comments regarding this Privacy Policy. If you have questions, comments or complaints regarding this Privacy Policy or the manner in which we treat your personal information, please contact our Chief Compliance Officer by email or postal mail at the following address:

Chief Compliance Officer  
Cintas Corporation  
6800 Cintas Boulevard  
P.O. Box 625737  
Cincinnati, Ohio 45262-5737  

##### Sole Statement

This Privacy Policy is the sole statement of our privacy policy with respect to our Services, and no summary, modification, restatement or other version thereof, or other privacy statement or policy, in any form, is valid unless we post a new or revised policy to the Services.

##### Additional Information for Nevada Residents

As outlined in this Privacy Policy, Cintas may collect personal information about you when you use the Site. Such information could include, among other things, your first and last name, home or physical address, email address, telephone number, and financial information needed to process payments if you make purchases, such as credit card or account information.

Although Cintas may share your personal information with certain third parties as outlined in this Privacy Policy, Cintas does not sell your personal information to any third parties for monetary consideration or share your personal information with any third parties that license or sell the information to additional persons.

If you are a Nevada resident, you may have the right to review and request changes to the personal information Cintas has collected about you. You also may have the right to direct Cintas not to sell your personal information. If Cintas begins selling personal data, this Privacy Policy will be revised to reflect that change and you will have the right to opt-out of the sale of your personal information.

You can exercise your rights by contacting:

Chief Compliance Officer  
Cintas Corporation  
6800 Cintas Boulevard  
P.O. Box 625737  
Cincinnati, Ohio 45262-5737  

Changes to this Privacy Policy will be posted on this Site, along with information on any material changes. Cintas reserves the right to update or modify this Privacy Policy at any time and without prior notice. Any modifications will apply only to the personal information we collect after the posting.
